<LoreBookDefinition>
<ItemID>-2906</ItemID>
<BookUID>trueflame.harmattan</BookUID>
<UseVisual>false</UseVisual>
<BookTitle>Old Harmattan, The Antique Plateau</BookTitle>
<BookTitlePageContent>
TrueFlame OC
</BookTitlePageContent>
<Pages>

  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle></PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
      Long ago, the Castle-like City of Harmattan, whose courtyard ever stands the vigil of the Sorobor Academy, was once much more.
      At one point, the outlying land was once a full city, complete with fine stone walls that protected its citizens from every hostility one could imagine, lights which rival the holy power of Elatt and many other amenities we folk have little knowledge of.
      While we imagine the Harmattan of today to be a culture of wealth, knowledge and more, in its older days all of this was far greater.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>

  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle></PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
      In the higher days of Harmattan, one could find numerous shops, homes and small farmsteads which grew wheat and purpkin patches, among other things that would delight even the finest of chefs.
      In this city, sumptuously built homesteads and streetlamps were powered by ancient magic and Golems powered by that source would walk the streets, not to harm, but instead help.
      Beyond this, one can see the remnants of the Hippodrome, a stadium to which the Ancient Soroboreans would watch races, undoubtedly between beast golems, and place bets towards or against their chosen steed. Although, more intriguing yet were the plays of Ancient Soroboreans, whom in their theatre one could only imagine the delights to which were very possibly preformed solely by Golems.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>

 <PageContent>
  <PageTitle></PageTitle>
  <TextContent>
    A shell, this Old Harmattan, now solely the Antique Plateau, remains filled with dangers everywhere.

    From undoubtedly common domestic animals such as the once noble Boozu and Veaber to, "newer," dangers like the Kazite Bandits and scourge remnants;

    Old Harmattan is a far cry from the safe haven it once was. And yet the dangers do not end there, for in the depths of the Antique Plateau reside the remains of this once proud people's greatest achievements and possibly greatest horrors.

    Within the dark reaches of Old Harmattan reside machines which whirl with life long after their creators have passed from this world, constant in their foreign, time-lost process.

    However, from what we can surmise, it is the very bones of what once was the powerhouse that was this ancient civilization.
    What expeditions have gone to these reaches have brought back advanced pieces of equipment which seem to suggest that our simplistic knowledge of the runic magics is but child's play before the knowledge and skilled craftsmanship of these Ancient Soroborean devices.

     And even with these devices, still we have such limited understanding of the process that we have yet to replicate it.
     What's worse is that we cannot easily acquire more, as what lurks beneath the surface makes expeditions incredibly dangerous and costly, thus for now we must accept theses advanced secrets of Old Harmattan as a mystery.
  </TextContent>
</PageContent>

<PageContent>
 <PageTitle></PageTitle>
 <TextContent>
  What we know for certain is Old Harmattan fell, and with it went a vast wealth of knowledge and information we have yet to recover.
  Although, in time, perhaps one day we will learn these secrets and the strange purple-shimmering skies will dot the vast landscape of all Aurai with purpose once more.
 </TextContent>
</PageContent>
</Pages>
</LoreBookDefinition>
