<LoreBookDefinition>
<ItemID>-2907</ItemID>
<BookUID>trueflame.berg</BookUID>
<BookDescription></BookDescription>
<UseVisual>false</UseVisual>
<BookTitle>The City of Berg</BookTitle>
<BookTitlePageContent>
  The City of Berg, by TrueFlame.
</BookTitlePageContent>
<Pages>
  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle>Berg: The Capital of the Blue Chamber Collective</PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
    There are few places in Aurai that can claim they are a family united in a similar purpose like Berg, the capital of the Blue Chamber Collective.
    However, Berg is less a capital and more a grand meeting hall for the various tribes and organizations which call themselves members of such an order.
    From small tribal towns, like Cierzo, to great economic powerhouses, like Harmattan, many are among the collective and it's aims to bring together the people of Aurai in a peaceful union.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>
  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle>Symbolism of Trust in Berg</PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
    The color blue is symbolic of trust, something common in berg, an expectation or a genuine feeling, each member of the collection relying on this most of all, the certainty of who to trust and the expectation of trust given.
    As such, its only fitting that almost every stone or tile has some trace shade of blue. This blue-tone even more-so of the entry gates, which from their blue-steel doors reflects the expectation that one should bring their trust with them when they enter such a place.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>
  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle>Amenities and Meeting Places in Berg</PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
    The streets, in common fashion for a major city, hold many sorts, from warriors to hunters of the region to citizens from all around, seeking to gain favor with one of the lords who sits upon a chamber chair.
    For an ambassadorial city, it has what amenities someone would need to live relatively comfortably there, the standard alchemist and food vendors, even a blacksmith.
    However, no comfort is as great as the inn residing in Berg, as it rests between the primary entrance of the city and the Blue Chamber itself.

    Perhaps the Old Coin Inn was so aptly named to remind those whose viewpoint is shared or misunderstood that at the end of the day everyone can spend some time at the inn and have a more relaxed talk over a fine drink.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>
  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle>The Blue Chamber and its Significance</PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
    And talks one will have, should you wander further up the stairs to the courtyard of blue and green surrounding a sheet of water in resemblance of purity, a finely carved stone monument of skulls and other iconography at its center, undoubtedly representative of the bond of family and the length of trust.
    Yet as awe-inspiring the view, it pales before the Blue Chamber itself, the great building which the collective take its name, built directly into the red-stone of the mountain-side.
    The chamber's great layered stone-brick segments painted various yellows and blues, covered in overgrowth of greenery sprouting up in places, a testament to such unending expectations built on trust.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>
  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle></PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
      Here, before all Aurai, do talks of the greatest magnitude unfold, the grand decider of entire cultures.

      Within this blue-stone structure reside many seats, adorned with banners from their representative's house in respect to those which they support.
      There at the room's center, a grand pedestal for those in talk to stand upon and be judged by other representing parties and mediated by the chamber speaker.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>

  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle>Final</PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
      Often, the complexity of the meeting can lead to members of each party bickering for hours till a choice is made, all beneath the light let in by either sun or moonlight pouring from the open canopy above.
      The grand scale of such a place and the craftsmanship of what resides there has few words to truly describe such a vista; it is a view for the ages.

      One could summarize Berg as being something quite special in its own right, though the message and direction which these people lead the blue chamber is most admirable indeed. If, in your travels, you find yourself in Berg, it is most wise to take time to reflect and perhaps share in the joyful union of communication.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>
</Pages>
</LoreBookDefinition>
