<LoreBookDefinition>
  <ItemID>-2932</ItemID>
  <BookUID>lorebook.huntersjournal.firstcannibal</BookUID>
  <BookDescription>This is a tattered old journal, specked with dirt and blood.</BookDescription>
  <UseVisual>false</UseVisual>
  <BookTitle>Tattered Cave Journal</BookTitle>
  <BookTitlePageContent>This is a tattered old journal, specked with dirt and blood. </BookTitlePageContent>
  <Pages>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle>Day 1</PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        We were so excited to explore this cave.
        My friends, Sarah and Jim, and I had always been adventurous and loved to explore new places, ever since we were little.
        We had heard rumors of a cave with a giant stone face in the Enmerkar Forest that was said to be filled with ancient treasures.
        Me and Sarah couldn't resist the opportunity to check it out, Jim didn't want to go, I teased him and called him a wimp eventually he agreed.

        We had a plan, Jim would bring food, Sarah would bring the rope and properly secure it, her papa is a sailor so she knows how to tie knots. I brought the lantern and my journal to document our finds.
        We arrived at the cave and began our descent. It was dark and damp, but we were determined to find something valuable.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle>Day 2</PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        We had no idea what we were getting ourselves into.
        Things have taken a turn for the worse.... Sarah didn't properly fasten the rope, apparently its all well and good knowing how to tie a knot correctly but that information becomes useless rather quickly when you forget to tie it at all.
        We've been stuck in this cave for three days now and we're running out of food.
        We've searched every inch of this cave and found nothing of value.
        We're beginning to think that we may not make it out of here alive.
        Why hasn't anyone come for us?
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle>Day 3</PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        Sarah suggested that we start rationing our food and water, which we didn't bring much of to begin with.
        I couldn't bear the thought of starving to death in this cave, so I agreed.
        But as the days passed and our food and water supplies dwindled, I began to feel a strange hunger. A hunger that I couldn't explain.
        I dont know if it's a fever from being trapped in here with nothing to eat and just this stagnant, green-ish hued water to drink.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle>Day 5</PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        It was either that or die of starvation. I know it's wrong, but I can't help the way I feel.

        Sarah was hesitant at first, Jim called us monsters.
        But eventually we all agreed to it, we're going to draw straws tomorrow if no one comes to resuce us..oh god.

        I know it's terrible and I'll never be able to forgive myself, but it seems like the only option.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle>Day 6</PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
          I drew the short straw.
          Sarah and Jim don't know yet they are too hungry to think straight before that even mattered a fight broke out, Jim screamed 'LOOK AT HOW AT SHES BEEN STARING AT US, LOOK AT HER EYES SARAH!'.
          Jim dropped his straw, I picked it up for him.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle>Day ????</PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        Jim is gone, Sarah hasn't been the same since, if it bothered her that much she shouldn't have ate.
        Sarah would be fine, Jim would be fine, I WOULD BE FINE! IF Sarah remembered to tie the rope.

        I keep blacking out, I suppose its to be expected, I don't think I have energy to even write anymore, nor much ink come to think on it.

        Why didn't she tie the rope, was she trying to kill us?
        The lantern is almost empty now, I seem to see better away from the light, its almost blinding.

        I can't stop thinking about the legend of the Wendigo.

        A powerful being, borne of the frost and vulnerable to only to the weapons wielded by the gods, lightning and fire.

        Unstoppable.

        Hungry.

        I must eat.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
  </Pages>
</LoreBookDefinition>
