<LoreBookDefinition>
  <ItemID>-2933</ItemID>
  <BookUID>lorebook.beastgolems</BookUID>
  <BookDescription>A biologist's study on the advanced magic and biology of Beast Golems</BookDescription>
  <UseVisual>false</UseVisual>
  <BookTitle>Gep's Study on Beast Golems: Mimicry of Natural Biology with Advanced Magic</BookTitle>
  <BookTitlePageContent>
    This study, conducted by biologist Gep, delves into the advanced magic and biology of Beast Golems, specifically focusing on a specific individual informally referred  to hereafter as "Rattles" due to a loose joint in its back right leg causing it to rattle while moving.
    (Note : And this is the only reason I am able to study it!)
  </BookTitlePageContent>
  <Pages>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle>Background on Beast Golems</PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
      Most of the Beast Golems were constructed in Harmattan and in the Electric Lab in Abrassar during the initial attack from The Scourge which struck Aurai around 100 years ago.
      The Golems were specifically designed to match the Scourge in combat, which can be seen in the visual resemblances as well as similar combat styles.
      </TextContent>
      <TextContent>
      I have heard rumour of the existence of other types of Golems created in other ways by powerful beings, but a man of my profession does not set any store by rumour!
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle>Common Attributes</PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
       Almost all Beast Golems are aggressive.
       Commonly immune to Bleeding and Poison effects.
       Usually resistant to Decay and vulnerable to Ethereal, with some exceptions.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle>Gep's Study</PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
       As a biologist, I was intrigued by the advanced magic and biology of the Beast Golems. I wanted to understand how they mimic natural biology with this advanced magic.
       If we are to accept the idea that their creators were capable of shaping them into all manner of forms, why a decidedly canine-like creature?

       However, after extensive research and examination of "rattles", I have unfortunately not found any new information that sheds light on this topic they simply remain a mystery of a higher order than my current understanding.
      </TextContent>
      <TextContent>
      The advanced magic used in their creation and maintenance seems to override any natural biological processes, making it impossible for me to draw any comparisons.
      This is incredibly frustrating, as it seems the secrets of the Beast Golems will remain a mystery.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
  </Pages>
</LoreBookDefinition>
