<LoreBookDefinition>
  <ItemID>-2909</ItemID>
  <BookUID>trueflame.levant</BookUID>
  <BookDescription></BookDescription>
  <UseVisual>false</UseVisual>
  <BookTitle>The Heroic Kingdom of Levant</BookTitle>
  <BookTitlePageContent>
  The Heroic Kingdom of Levant, by TrueFlame.
  </BookTitlePageContent>
  <Pages>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle></PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        Levant, a Diamond in the rough, is a city found deep in the Abrassar desert, a veritable oasis in an inhospitable land. Every surface and statue a shining jewel for the eye to behold. Truly a marvel of our time in both its size and wealth, as even the price of life is high in Levant. Even the Levantine inn boasts a life of finery, complete with beautiful women to take in as you enjoy a drink.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle></PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        People of all sorts walk the streets, from merchant lords to commoners, many there for luxury or trade and others there for business and personal matters. Beyond this, Levant boasts some of the finest craftsmen in all Aurai, with Armorers, Gunsmiths and Master alchemists abound, all willing to assist you in whatever way they can... for a price.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle></PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        Even the guards dress in fineries, clad in garb of fine cloths draped in exquisite metals edged in gold with weapons layered in marble and other valuable adornments. The guards stand ever-ready in their gold-feathered hats, waiting patiently for the moment of their need. Most notably is their stature, as the common guard in Levant is impressively large, towering over the common man like demi-gods from their mountaintops.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle></PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        The Levantine Guard must be ready to protect their King and Queen, who reside within the Heroes' Palace. The Palace is a great towering structure which can be seen from the Desert itself, its great dome easily in view from far within the desert. The Palace of Heroes' also serves as a shining beacon of paradise in the vastness of the golden sands, the exterior adorned in fineries as much as those who guard it.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle></PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        King Simeon and Queen Calixa, who sit upon their thrones of marble and hand-crafted wood and metals, peer out towards any who would visit them, always ready for the worst. The King and Queen's weapons, like fineries, draped at their sides in waiting, ready as any Hero would, for a moment's notice. To their left, their loyal advisor, Kirouac, stands awaiting any sort of wisdom his King and Queen might need, his mind ever deep in thought.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle></PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        Yet to the southern side of the city resides the slums, a place filled with pain, poverty and strife where, like the desert, the weak perish under the insurmountable heat of the sun. Death is common here among such folk, as few have money, skill or the means to better themselves and have no choice but to sit and wait for an untimely end. Life is hard here and rarely does it improve, these poor folk damned to live out their lives in a place they've little hope to escape from, the city a gilded prison and the sands a gilded death sentence.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
    <PageContent>
      <PageTitle></PageTitle>
      <TextContent>
        Yet even in the Slums of Levant do secrets rest for those who seek them, much like the vast mystery that lay within the Abrassar. To those clever enough to find them, such secrets could in-fact provide many a great boon and even, humorously, vast wealth... Yet there are a few secrets which reside in the slums that may very well decide the fate of many a soul, both in Levant and beyond.

        Levant, a city which many visit to become Heroes, full of wealth and secrets for those who know where to look.
      </TextContent>
    </PageContent>
  </Pages>
</LoreBookDefinition>
