<LoreBookDefinition>
<ItemID>-2908</ItemID>
<BookUID>trueflame.abrassar</BookUID>
<BookDescription></BookDescription>
<UseVisual>false</UseVisual>
<BookTitle>The Abrassar Desert</BookTitle>
<BookTitlePageContent>
  The Abrassar Desert, by TrueFlame.
</BookTitlePageContent>
<Pages>
  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle></PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
      The calm, quiet of the Abrassar desert is a solmn reminder of solitude, the golden sands stretching endlessly on, wind kicking up every grain and shuffling it about like waves at sea. It is a place of calm and meditation, a place where the mind can wander alone and at peace, to think upon one's self and their surroundings. It is said that here Elatt once dwelled and did exactly that, ponder on himself and the world.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>
  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle></PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
    In the Abrassar desert, only the hardiest of things live, such as sand raiders and assassin beetles... or vile crescent sharks who float across the sands. A harsh and dangerous land for the unprepared that will sap away your very stamina if not ready for it. Keep watch for what you can here to help you survive it's hunger for weaker souls. Everything from cactus fruit to Jewel Bird meat holds some grain of knowledge which shall impart another count towards the flame that is your life.
  </TextContent>
  </PageContent>
  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle></PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
    And if your life you value, you will do well to avoid the ancient places hidden in the Abrassar, like the walled garden or the colossal hive... or even old Levant, as all hold dangers which seek to take you for themselves, another mystery beheld only to the sands. It is wise to seek out safe havens and places of shelter if you travel there, especially under the light of day.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>
  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle></PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
    However, even nightfall offers its hardships, as the cool air of the desert makes travel yet another trouble entirely. This place, the Abrassar Desert, is as much a test, as Monsoon, in its every step. Take care to prepare well and you may just prosper in these unforgiving lands. While rife with troubles, it is also filled with treasures.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>
  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle></PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
    It is said that once the Abrassar Desert was no desert at all, once a lush and vibrant land full of life, like Chersonese or Enmerkar. With time, the Abrassar dried up, the water once bearing ships replaced for a sea of sand, leaving only their remnants behind. Upon inspection of the horizon, one might see the many crumbled buildings or even a statue swallowed up by the sands, its former glory lost forever.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>
  <PageContent>
    <PageTitle></PageTitle>
    <TextContent>
      While harsh, it is the land of Heroes, and aptly named, as only those of stronger stock would dare to dwell in such as hard land far from the comforts of the world. And yet, these hardship are the Levantine way, the struggle to overcome great odds through sheer will and triumph alone.
      It is a mystery what happened to the Abrassar of old, yet now it is a place of ancient treasures and many secrets lost beneath the sands.
    </TextContent>
  </PageContent>
</Pages>
</LoreBookDefinition>
